Our second strategy will be to develop
第二个策略是使用函数逼近
a temporal difference technique with function approximation.
构建一个时间差分技巧
Compare the incremental update step between Monte Carlo learning,
比较蒙特卡洛学习的递增更新步骤
where we use the actual return obtained through the episode
（使用在阶段中获得的实际回报）
with the temporal difference case where we use an estimated return.
与时间差分的更新步骤（使用估算回报）
This is called the TD target.
这叫做 TD 目标
And in the simplest case, TD zero,
在最简单的形式 TD(0) 下
we use the next reward plus the discounted value of the next state.
我们使用下个奖励和下个状态的折扣值
In a similar manner as before,
和之前的方法类似
we can use this TD target in place of our unknown true value function.
我们可以使用这个 TD 目标替换未知真值函数
This gives us something concrete to work with.
这样就可以使用具体的数据
No more articles or other imaginary creatures.
不再是想象的数据
Note that we had to adapt the value function to use our function approximator V hat.
注意 我们需要调整值函数 才能使用函数逼近器 v^
This entire difference is called the TD error and denoted by
这整个差值称之为 TD 误差 表示为 δt
delta T. We can extend the same idea to action value functions as well.
我们也可以将同一概念应用到动作值函数
All right, we're ready to build an algorithm around this update rule.
我们已经准备好围绕这个更新规则构建一个算法
We'll use a TD zero target and focus on the control problem again.
我们将使用 TD(0) 目标并再次侧重于控制问题
As you may recall,
你可能还记得
this is essentially the SARSA algorithm.
这本质上是 SARSA 算法
We begin by initializing our parameters W arbitrarily.
我们首先随机地初始化参数 W
Our policy PI is implicitly defined as an epsilon
策略 π 隐式地定义为
greedy choice over our approximate action value function Q hat.
针对估算动作值函数 Q^ 的 Epsilon 贪婪选择
Then, we start interacting with the environment.
然后我们开始与环境互动
For each episode, we begin with some initial state S obtained from the environment.
对于每个阶段 我们以从环境获得的初始状态 S 开始
We continue interacting till we reach a terminal state.
我们继续互动 直到抵达最终状态
At each time step,
在每个时间步
we choose an action A to perform and observe the reward R and next state S prime.
我们选择执行一个动作 A 并获得奖励 R 和下个状态 S′
Now, we choose another action A prime,
现在根据 Epsilon 贪婪策略 π
this time from state S prime according to our epsilon greedy policy PI.
从状态 S′ 选择另一个动作 A′
This gives us all we need for the SARSA update,
这样就获得了 SARSA 更新所需的一切
S, A, R, S prime, A prime.
即 S A R S′ A′
We plug these into our gradient descent update rule and adjust our weights accordingly.
将这些项代入梯度下降更新规则并相应地调整权重
Finally, we simply roll over S prime to be the new S,
最后 直接将 S′ 替换为新的 S
A prime to be the new A and repeat.
将 A′ 替换为新的 A 并重复刚刚的流程
This formulation is useful for
这个公式适用于阶段性任务
episodic tasks where each episode is guaranteed to terminate.
在阶段性任务中 每个阶段都肯定会终止
It can be adapted to continuing tasks by eliminating the distinct boundary
这个公式可以经过调整并应用于连续性任务
between episodes and treating the sequence of interactions as one long unending episode.
方法是消除阶段之间的界限并将一系列的动作当做一个很长的无止境阶段
SARSA is an on policy algorithm.
SARSA 是一种异同策略算法
Which means that we are updating
表示我们的更新策略
the same policy that we are following to carry out actions.
和执行动作时遵守的策略一样
This usually works very well and converges pretty quickly
通常效果很好并且能快速收敛
because you are using the most updated policy to take each decision.
因为你会根据最新的策略执行动作
But this also has some drawbacks,
但是也有一些缺点
mainly that the policy being learned and the one
主要是学习的策略
being followed are intimately tied to each other.
和遵守的策略关系太紧密
What if we wanted to follow one policy,
如果我们想遵守一个策略 例如更加探索性的策略
say one that is more exploratory while learning the more optimal policy?
并学习更加优化的策略呢
That's where we need off policy algorithms.
这时候就需要用到离线策略算法